Class of 1906 Records, 1902-1971
Smith College Archives
Class of 1906 Records
1902-1971
Smith College. Class of 1906.
RG 80 UUID:ca799837-4a6f-4f33-a340-fe0694d8c5f7
24 boxes (11.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 24 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1906.
The Class of 1906 was the twenty-eighth entering class and the twenty-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1906 records, 1902-1971, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1906, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, financial information, minutes, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1906 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Alumnae Fund List 1956-1964 (Box 1684, Folder 1)
- Baccalaureate 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 2)
- Sophomore Basketball Team 1904 (Box 1684, Folder 3)
- Class Letters 1926-1963 (Box 1684, Folder 4)
- Fund Letters 1923-1966 (Box 1684, Folder 5)
- Groups 1902-1906 (Box 1684, Folder 6)
- Regional Lists 1968-1969 (Box 1684, Folder 7)
- Scholarships and Bequests 1960-1969 (Box 1684, Folder 8)
- Class Secretary's Notebook 1902-1921 (Box 1684, Folder 9)
- Smith College Relief Unit 1918 (Box 1684, Folder 10)
- Class Supper 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 11)
- Commencement 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 12)
- Commencement Music 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 13)
- Commencement Speaker 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 14)
- Freshman Grind by 1905 1902 (Box 1684, Folder 15)
- Freshman Handbook 1902-1903 (Box 1684, Folder 16)
- Granddaughter's Scarf, Clubs 1941, undated (Box 1684, Folder 17)
- History undated (Box 1684, Folder 18)
- Ivy Day 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 19)
- Ivy Day Photos 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 20)
- Junior Frolic 1905 (Box 1684, Folder 21)
- Junior Prom 1905 (Box 1684, Folder 22)
- Meeting Minutes 1961-1969 (Box 1684.1, Folder 1)
- Necrology undated (Box 1684.1, Folder 2)
- Officers undated (Box 1684.1, Folder 3)
- Organization undated (Box 1684.1, Folder 4)
- President's Notebook 1906-1956 (Box 1684.1, Folder 5)
- Songs undated (Box 1684.1, Folder 6)
- Sophomore Reception 1902 (Box 1684.1, Folder 7)
- Treasurer's Records 1902-1943 (Box 1684.1, Folder 8)
- Treasurer's Reports 1906-1961 (Box 1684.1, Folder 9)
- Reunions undated (Box 1685, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1907 (Box 1685, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1909 (Box 1685, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1911 (Box 1685, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1916 (Box 1685, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1921 (Box 1685, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1925 (Box 1685, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1929 (Box 1685, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1931 (Box 1685, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1931 (Box 1685, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1934 (Box 1685, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1936 (Box 1685, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1941 (Box 1685, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1941 (Box 1685, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1946 (Box 1685.1, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1951 (Box 1685.1, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1956 (Box 1685.1, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1961 (Box 1685.1, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1966 (Box 1685.1, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1971 (Box 1685.1, Folder 6)
- Reunions- General undated (Box 1685.1, Folder 7)
- Reunions- Songs undated (Box 1685.1, Folder 8)
- Reunion Materials undated (Box 1685.1, Folder 9)
- Senior Dramatics 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 5)
- Senior Dramatics 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 6)
- Senior Dramatics- Smith College Club of New York 1907 (Box 1686, Folder 7)
- Senior Dramatics 1907 (Box 1686, Folder 8)
- Banner and Memorabilia (Box OV)